var data = [
  {
    "category": "Montana 2016",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<p>What drug caused Montana Mendy to throw his MacBook away ina publish trashcan? </p><ol><li>Xanax</li><li>Vyvanse</li><li>St Johns Wort</li><li>All of the above</li></ol>",
        "answer": "D. All of the Above"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "This seems _________",
        "answer": "Insane"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "The girl that Montana want's to respond, but NEVER does",
        "answer": "Sylvia"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Montana uses a certain type of drug, to mainly relax him when he goes to FedEx-Kinkos",
        "answer": "Klonopin"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Montana 2015",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<p>How much are Montana's FedEx-Kinko shopping spree's usually?",
        "answer": "$250-300 USD"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Favorite kind of natural tea Montana dips in tea with neutral facial expression",
        "answer": "Chai something tea" 
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<p>True or False, has Montana Mendy ever crawled on the floor to find a .7mg Xanax on BART",
        "answer":  "True"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "True or False, Montana Mendy is banned from The New Yorker parties",
        "answer": "True"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Montana 2013",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "In 2013 did Montana multiply 5x5 without any time constraints and answer 64?",
        "answer":   "Yes"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "In 2013, did Montana Mendy go to Facebook Campus tell Mark Zuckerberg his nickname should be memcahced",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "Does Montana Mendy remember 2013?",
        "answer":  "No"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What was Montana Mendy's 2013 hit on Stickam for 1 day before Stickam shut it doors?",
        "answer": "livin la vida coleslaw" 
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Feeling Lucky",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "Does Montana Mendy like Xanax or Ativan to treat his anxiety disorder?",
        "answer":   "Xanax"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "How often does Montana Mendy leave the house?",
        "answer":   "1x a week"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "How many times has Montana pushed to GitHub with glazed eyes",
        "answer": "3 confirmed"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Does Montana Mendy prefer Ruby on Rails or Django?",
        "answer": "Django"
      }
    ]
  }
];